Register to The Harold Rome Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Music by Rome, 1935-1981; Series I; 24.2' (58 boxes)
  - Stage Works, I.A
    - [Destry rides again. Once knew a fella; arr.] Once knew a fella: fox-trot: From the New, 35 parts; 27 cm. (Box 11, Folder 81)
      Arranged for flute, oboe, B-flat clarinet 1-4, bassoon, 1st E-flat alto saxophone, 2nd B-flat tenor saxophone, 3rd E-flat alto saxophone, 4th B-flat tenor saxophone, 5th E-flat baritone saxophone, horn, B-flat trumpet 1-3 (6), trombone 1-3 (6), vocal, piano, guitar, violin (2), violin A-B - conductor (2), violin C (2), viola, violoncello, and double bass
    - [Destry rides again. Selections. Vocal score], 1955-1958; 1 manuscript vocal score (269 p. in various pagings); 32 cm. (Box 11, Folder 82-83)
      Holograph in pencil and ink and manuscript (in part, photocopies)
      Includes sketches and five sheets of lyrics (typescript)
      Note on envelope: Destry Rides Again originals + worksheets
      Phone number on folder within envelope: OR4 3865
    - [Destry rides again. Vocal score] Destry Rides Again / Music and Lyrics by Harold Rome; Book by Leonard Gershe; Orchestrations by Phillip J. Lang; Dance Music Arranged by Genevieve Pitot. -- 1959., 1 manuscript vocal score (234 p.), bound; 33 cm. (Box 11, Folder 84)
      Manuscript (photocopy)
      Note by Rome on title page: Conductor's score - Harold Rome
      Date appears on the bottom of a few pages
      Contents: New Destry Overture. Bottleneck. Bottleneck Tag. We're Ladies. Honky-Tonk Piano. Hoop-De-Dingle. New Dingle #8. Dingle 11. Dingle # 13. Tomorrow morning (transposed). We're Ladies - Reprise. Ballad of a gun. The Social. Whip Dance. Social-Coda. Social Tag-Minor. Tomorrow-Change. I Know Your Kind. I Hate Him (transposed). Hoop De Dingle-Utility. Hoop De Dingle (Utility). Paradise Alley. Kind-Tag. Anyone Would Love You. Anyone-Tag. Once Knew A Fella. Once Knew A Fella (Utility). Every Once In A While. Every Once In A While (Utility). Fair Warning (N.Y.). Gun-Reprise. New Entr'acte. I Say Hello (Utility). Every Once In A While (Utility). Are You Ready. Not Guilty. Ready Tag. Only Time Will Tell (New B ). Only Time Will Tell Tag. Dingle #36B. Respectability (Utility). Respectability. Ring On The Finger. Anyone Tag. Once Knew A Fella (Reprise). I Say Hello (Revised). Hoop De Dingle Dirge. After, Dirge. Gun-Reprise #46
    - [Destry rides again. Vocal score] Destry: preliminary rehearsal score / Harold Rome., 1 manuscript vocal score (114 p.) in various pagings; 32 cm. (Box 11, Folder 85)
      Card stapled to cover signed by Rome
      Contents: Opening-Bottleneck. We're ladies. We're ladies (Last Chorus). Hoop-De-Dingle (Introduction). Hoop De Dingle. Tomorrow Morning (Interlude). Tomorrow Morning. Swap her for a mule. A Handy Thing. I Know Your Kind. I Hate Him. Let's Talk About a Woman. Rose Lovejoy of Paradise Alley. Anyone would love you. Once Knew A Fella. Every Once In A While. Fair Warning. Ballad Of A Gun. Are You Ready. Not Guilty. Only Time Will Tell. Respectability. Ring On The Finger. Once Too Long Ago
    - [Fanny. Fanny. French & English] Fanny: Medium Slow / de Harold Rome; Paroles françaises de René Rouzaud. -- Paris: Chappell, c1954., 10 parts; 27 cm. (Box 12, Folder 86)
      Includes parts for alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone, trumpet 1-2, trombone, accordion-violin (includes French lyrics), piano-conductor (includes English lyrics), guitar, and double bass
      Pl. no.: C.S.A. 4722
      With: Come rain or come shine (Mercer/Arlen)
    - [Fanny. Fanny; arr.] Fanny: Fox-trot: From the Musical Comedy "Fanny" / Words and Music by Harold Rome; a masterscore arrangement dance and vocal background arr. by Johnny Warrington. -- New York: Chappell & Co., c1954., 35 parts; 27 cm. (Box 12, Folder 86)
      Arranged for flute (2), oboe (2), bassoon, 1st alto saxophone (2), 2nd tenor saxophone (2), 3rd alto saxophone (2), 4th tenor saxophone (2), 5th baritone saxophone (2), horn 1 & 2, trumpet 1-2 (6), trombone 1-3 (6), drums, vocal, piano, guitar, violin A-C (2), viola, violoncello, and double bass
    - [Fanny. I have to tell you; arr.] I have to tell you: Fox-trot: From the Musical Comedy "Fanny" / Words and Music by Harold Rome; a masterscore arrangement dance and vocal background arr. by Johnny Warrington. -- N.Y.: Chappell & Co., Inc., c1954., 65 parts; 27 cm. (Box 12, Folder 87)
      Arranged for flute (2), oboe (2), clarinet 1-3, 5 (8), bass clarinet (2), bassoon (2), 1st alto saxophone, 2nd tenor saxophone, 3rd alto saxophone, 4th tenor saxophone, 5th baritone saxophone, horn 1 & 2 (2), trumpet 1-3 (9), trombone 1-3 (9), drums, vocals (male and female), piano (3), guitar (3), violin A-B (conductor) (2), violin A-C (2), viola (2), violoncello (2), and double bass
      Includes parts arranged for "Fox trot" and both male (C) and female (A-flat) vocals
    - [Fanny. Restless heart; arr.] Restless heart: Fox-trot: From the Musical Comedy "Fanny" / Words and Music by Harold Rome; a masterscore arrangement dance and vocal background arr. by Johnny Warrington. -- N.Y.: Chappell & Co., c1954., 65 parts; 27 cm. (Box 12, Folder 88)
      Arranged for flute (2), oboe (2), clarinet 1-3, 5 (8), 5th bass clarinet (2), 1st alto saxophone, 2nd tenor saxophone, 3rd alto saxophone, 4th tenor saxophone, 5th baritone saxophone, horn 1-2 (2), trumpet 1-3 (5), trombone 1-3 (9), drums, vocals (2), piano (2), violin-conductor (2), violin A-C (2), violin C (2), viola (2), violoncello (2), and double bass (2)
      Includes parts arranged for male (C) and female (A-flat) vocals
    - [Fanny. Vocal score] Fanny: Preliminary Rehearsal Score. -- c1954., 1 manuscript vocal score (63 p. in various pagings), bound; 32 cm. (Box 12, Folder 89)
      Manuscript (photocopy), signed [cover]
      Contents: Restless Heart. Poor Paris! Welcome Home. Why Be Afraid to Dance Verse. Why be afraid to dance. Octopus. Never Too Late For Love. Cold Cream Jar Song (Sung by Panisse). I Like You. I have to tell you. Fanny. Oysters, Cockles and Mussels. Panisse and Son. Happy Birthday Round. To My Wife. Verse to Reprise of "I Have To Tell You." Love is a very light thing. Verse to Reprise of Fanny. Be Kind to your Parents
    - [Fanny. Welcome home; arr.] Welcome Home: from "Fanny" / Words and Music by Harold Rome; Arranged for Orchestra by Jimmy Lally -- London: Chappell & Co., Ltd., c1956., 15 parts; 27 cm. (Box 12, Folder 90)
      Arranged for: alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, trumpet 1-3, trombone 1-2, drums, piano, guitar, violin A-C (2), and double bass
      Pl. no.: 43562
    - [Gone with the wind. English] Scarlett / Words and Music by Harold Rome. -- 1968-1969., 1 manuscript score (52 p. in various pagings); 32 cm. (Box 12, Folder 91)
      Holograph and manuscript (photocopy), in part signed
      With piano accompaniment
      Note on title page: First original rehearsal piano score Oct. 1969
      Contents: 1A I love you. 2 We belong to you. 3 Scarlett. 4 Southern hymn. 4a Bonnie blue flag round. 5 Two of a kind. 6 Blissful Christmas. 6A My soldier. 7 Lovely stranger. 8 A time for love. 8A What is love? 9 Gambling man. 10 Which way is home. 11 O"Hara. 12 Sister brother. 13 The newlywed's song. 14 Strange and wonderful. 15 Blueberry eyes. 16 Little wonders. 17 Bonnie gone
    - [Gone with the wind. English] Scarlett / Harold Rome. -- 1969-1973., 1 manuscript score (57 p. in various pagings); 28-32 cm. (Box 12, Folder 92)
      Holographs, signed, in pencil and ink (in part, photocopies)
      Note on discarded envelope: Scarlett original manuscripts for later piano score Aug-Oct 1969
      Includes list of musical numbers
      Contents [numbers in brackets are those which appear on the list which is laid in - all c1969 unless otherwise noted]: 8 [1] A time for love. 8A [2] What is love? 9 [3] Gambling man. 10 [4] Which way is home. 11 [5] O'Hara. 6 [12] Sister brother. 13 [7] The newlywed's song. [8] Strange and wonderful. 16 [9] Little wonders. Bonnie gone intro. 17 [10] Bonnie gone. 7 [11] Lonely stranger. 6A [12] My soldier. 6 [13] Blissful Christmas. 5 [14] Two of a kind. 4 [15] Southern hymn. 1A [16] Love you. How lucky (photocopy), c1973. Soldier's goodbye (photocopy), 1973 Jul. 22
    - [Gone with the wind. English] Gone with the wind / Harold Rome. -- ca. 1973 Aug. 20., 1 manuscript score (259 p. in various pagings); 33 cm. (Box 12, Folder 93-95)
      Score (holograph, signed) and sketch in pencil for "Let's talk about a woman" laid in
      Note on score: GWTW USA
      Lists of musical numbers for Los Angeles, London, and Dallas productions, as well as "Jay Blackton's book" laid in (copies, originals with Production Materials)
      Contents [in the order in which they were found]: Let's talk about a woman (sketch). Let's talk about a woman - revised. No. 2 Today's the day. No. 1 "Overture" (Note: O.K. 8/20/73). 3 We belong to you. 4 Scarlett. 6B Quadrille - Pt. 1. 6C Quadrille - Part II. 7 Two of a kind. 9 Blissful Xmas. 9B Atlanta Station. 10 Lonely stranger. 11 Atlanta Station - Pt. 2. 12 Lonely stranger reprise. #14 Curtain - Act I. 16 Entr'acte. 18 Gone with the wind. 19A How lucky. 19B Southern lady Part 29 19D Marrying for fun. 20 Brand new friends. 20B Miss Fiddle Dee Dee. #21 Blueberry eyes. #24 After Bonnie. 24A It doesn't matter now. 17 How often. Gone with the wind - show order. Ending for Brand new friends. Exit music. 22 Pre Bonnie. 17 How often key of F. 17 How often key of E-flat
    - [Gone with the wind. English] G.W.T.W.: USA. -- 1973., 1 manuscript score (368 p. in various pagings); 33 cm. (Box 13, Folder 96-100)
      On cover: rehearsal piano
      Note: G.W.T.W. USA
      Contents: No. 1 Overture. No. 2 Today's the day. 2A Cake walk. 3 We belong to you. 4 Scarlett. 5 Intro "We Belong" reprise. 5A Bugle scene change. 6A Reel I. 6B Quadrille - Pt. 1. 6C Quadrille part II. 7 Two of a kind. 7A Reel II. 8 Two of a kind reprise. 9 Blissful Christmas. 9A Farewell. 9B Atlanta Station. 10 Lonely stranger reprise. 13 Atlanta burning. #14 Curtain - Act I. #16
      New Entr'acte. #16A Opening - Act II New. Old #16A (Note: use for piano rehearsal only - possible pit piano). 17 How often. 19A/B How lucky. Southern lady new. #19C Southern lady part II. 19D Marrying for fun. #20 Brand new friends. 20B Miss Fiddle Dee Dee. #21 Blue berry eyes. #22 Gone with the wind. #23 Bonnie gone. #24 After Bonnie. 24A It doesn't matter now. #25 Finale ultimo. Bows music. Exit music
    - [Gone with the wind. English] Gone With The Wind / Music and Lyrics by Harold Rome; Book by Horton Foote. -- 1973-1976., 1 manuscript score (285 p.), bound; 28 cm. (Box 14, Folder 101)
      Note on table of contents page: Dallas 1976 Final copy
      Contents: 1 Overture. #2 Today's the day. 2A Fun and games. 2B Cakewalk. 2C We belong to you. 4 Scarlett. 5 Intro "We belong" reprise. 5A Battle insert. 6A Quadrille. 7 Two of a kind. 7A Polonaise. 8 Two of a kind reprise. 9 Blissful Christmas. 10 Passing through / orchestration by Bill Brohn (condensed score). 11 Tomorrow is another day. 12 Atlanta burning. 13 If only. 15 Entr'acte. 16 A time for love. 17 Southern lady part I. 17A Southern lady part II. 18 Marrying for fun. 19 New Orleans dance. 20 Strange and wonderful. 20A Mansion reveal. 21 Blueberry eyes. 22. The lady is lucky / Brohn orchestration (condensed score). 22A The lady is lucky reprise. 23 Bonnie gone. 23A Bonnie gone insert. 24 Finale ultimo. 25 Bows
    - [Gone with the wind. English; arr.], 1972-1973; 1 manuscript condensed score (337 p. in various pagings) + 51 parts; 33 cm. (Box 14, Folder 102-157, Box 15, Box 16, Box 17, Box 18, Box 19, Box 20, Box 21, Box 22)
      Manuscript (photocopies) with markings and original manuscript in pencil and ink
      Score includes musical numbers arranged with piano accompaniment
      Most parts were labeled "Houston use," "Houston don't use," "Yes," or "No" - this is noted on the folders
      Contents: 1 Overture. #2 Today's the day. 2A Fun and games. 2B Cake walk. 2C We belong to you. 4 Scarlett. 5 Intro "We belong reprise." 5A Battle insert. 6 Reel. 6A Quadrille. 7 Two of a kind. 7A Polonaise. 8 Two of a kind. 9 Blissful Christmas. 10 Passing through (orchestration by Bill Brohn). 11 Tomorrow. 12 Ashley's departure. Ballet B. 13 Atlanta burning. 13 If only. 14 Finale Act I. 15A Reconstruction. 15 Entr'acte. 16 A time for love. #16A Opening - Act II New. 17 Southern lady - part 1. 17A Southern lady part II. 18 Marrying for fun. 19 New Orleans dance. 20 Strange and wonderful. 20A Mansion reveal. 20B Dance before lucky lady. #21 Blueberry eyes. 21A Cue: Applause. 21C Cue: I haven't any excuse... 22 The lady is lucky. 22A Lady is lucky reprise. 23 Intro Bonnie gone. #24 Finale ultimo. 25 Bows
    - [Gone with the wind. English; arr.], 1973; 1 manuscript condensed score (323 p. in various pagings) + 22 parts; 33 cm. (Box 23, Folder 158-188, Box 24, Box 25, Box 26, Box 27)
      Manuscript (photocopies, in part originals) with markings
      Includes duplicate scores, some with piano accompaniment and some transposed
      Miscellaneous parts and score at end
      Discarded folders labeled "USA"
      Discarded trunk had sticker which read "Theatre Under the Stars Houston, TX"
      Contents [condensed score unless otherwise noted]: No. 1 Overture. No. 2 Today's the day (2 copies, 1 with piano accompaniment). 3 We belong to you (2 copies). 4 Scarlett (2 copies). 5 Intro "We belong" Reprise. 5A Bugle scene change (3 copies). 6B Quadrille - Pt. 1. 6C Quadrille - Part II. 7A Reel II. 8 Two of a kind reprise. 9 Blissful Christmas. 9B Atlanta Station (3 copies). 10 Lonely stranger (2 copies, 1 with piano accompaniment). 11 Atlanta Station - Pt. 2 (2 copies). 12 Lonely Stranger reprise (3 copies). #14 Curtain - Act I. 15 Entr'acte (2 copies, 1 incomplete). #16 New Entr'acte. #16A Opening - Act II (5 copies - 3 different scores, and 1 with piano accompaniment). #17 How often. 18 Taxes. #19 End - Ashley scene (3 copies, 1 with piano accompaniment). 19 A/B How lucky. 19B [crossed out] 17 Southern lady part 1. #19D Marrying for fun (2 copies). 20 Brand new friends (4 copies, 1 with piano accompaniment). #20B Miss Fiddle-Dee-Dee (5 copies, 3 of which are with piano accompaniment). #21 Blueberry eyes. 22 Pre Bonnie (2 copies). #23 Bonnie's gone. #23 Bonnie gone - Intro and Chorus. #24 After Bonnie (2 copies). #24A It doesn't matter now (2 copies, 1 with piano accompaniment). #24B Finale ultimo. #25 Finale ultimo (2 copies). 24 Finale ultimo. #22 Gone with the wind reprise. 18 Gone with the wind. Exit music (2 copies)
    - [Gone with the wind. English & Japanese], 1969 Dec. 22; 1 manuscript score (242 p. in various pagings); 36 cm. (Box 27, Folder 189-191, Box 28)
      Holograph and manuscript (photocopy)
      Book by Kazuo Kikuta [from Dallas 1976 score]
      At end: Finito tutta la cosa! Hallelulia! 12/22/1969 Tokyo, Jap T.R.
      Note clipped to 1st page: 2A Cakewalk sent to Mr. Rome 7/27/73
      Contents: 1 Overture. #1 He loves me. 4 Scarlett intro. 4 Scarlett. 4A Tara. 5 Intro "We belong" reprise. 5A Bugle scene change. 6 Bazaar-hymn. 6A/7A Reel. 6B Atlanta station. 9 ? Waiting for Ashley. 10 Lonely stranger. 11 A time for love (new). 12 What is love. 13 Atlanta burning. 14 Gambling man. 15 Which way is home. 17 O'Hara. 17A Reconstruction ballet. 18 Newlywed song. 18A Riverboat sequence II. 22 Little wonders. 21 Blueberry eyes. Bonnie gone. 24 After Bonnie. 25 Finale ultimo
    - [Gone with the wind. English & Japanese], 1969 Dec. 22; 1 manuscript score (362 p. in various pagings); 37 cm. (Box 28, Folder 192-194)
      Holograph and manuscript (photocopy), in part in pencil, with pencil and ink additions
      Note on discarded folder: Trude GWTW Tokyo 1969
      At end: Finito tutta la cosa. Hallelulia! 12/22/1969 Tokyo, Japan T.R.
      Contents: 1 Overture. 2 Bazaar-hymn. #2 Today's the day. 4 Scarlett. 2A Cakewalk. 3 Intro "We belong to you." 3 Pt. II We belong to you. 4 Scarlett intro. 4A Tara. 5 Intro "We belong" reprise. 5 We belong. 5A Bugle scene change. 6 Bazaar-hymn. 6A + 7A Reel. 6B Quadrille. 7 Dance insert Two of a kind. 8 Two of a kind. 7 Two of a kind. 9 Blissful Christmas. 9A Waiting for Ashley. Farewell. 9B Atlanta Station. 10 Lonely stranger. 4 Scarlett (note: obsolete London). Intro Strange and wonderful. A time for love (new). 14 Gambling man. 15 Which way is home. 15A Curtain Act I old. 17 O'Hara. 17A Reconstruction ballet. 17B Gambling man - reprise. 20 Strange and wonderful. 17D-19A Riverboat sequence. 19 Newlywed song. 21 Blueberry eyes. 22 Little wonders. 24 After Bonnie. 25 Finale ultimo
    - [Gone with the wind. English & Japanese], 1969; 1 manuscript score (333 p. in various pagings); 36 cm. (Box 29, Folder 195-197)
      Holograph and manuscript (photocopy) with markings
      Note on discarded folder: 2 Scarlett rehearsal score Rome
      Contents [in the order in which it was found]: 1 Overture. 6 Bazaar-hymn. #2 He loves me. 2A Cakewalk. 3 Trans. + Intro to "We belong to you (Kupferman). 3 We belong to you. 4A Tara. 5 Intro "We belong" reprise. 5A Bugle scene change. 6 Bazaar-hymn. 6A 7A Reel into 8 Two of a kind. 8 Two of a kind. 9 Blissful Christmas. 9 Blissful Christmas choral. Atlanta Station. 9B Ballet. 9A Waiting for Ashley. 10 Lonely stranger. 11 A time for love. 13 Atlanta burning. 14 Gambling man. 15 Which way is home. Curtain Act 1. 17 Shantytown. 17B Gambling man - reprise. Reconstruction. 17C Underscore - Act II. 20 Strange and wonderful. 21 Blueberry eyes. 23 Bonnie gone. 24 After Bonnie. 25 Finale ultimo. 17D Riverboat sequence. 18A Riverboat sequence II. 19 Newlywed's song.
    - [Gone with the wind. English & Japanese. Selections; arr.], 1 manuscript score (896 p. in various pagings); 39 cm. (Box 95)
      Manuscript, in part signed by Meyer Kupferman, in [pencil and ink (in part, photocopies) and holographs (photocopies)
      Arranged for orchestra by Meyer Kupferman
      Also includes sketches, and sheets with notes
      Contents [in order in which they were found]: 17D-19A Riverboat sequence I (Two of a kind reprise) (spiral bound photocopy). #1 Shantytown. Two of a kind. 1 Overture. 21 Blueberry eyes. Bonnie gone. 25 Finale ultimo: piano not required. 17 O'Hara. 10 Lonely stranger. 11 A time for love. 15A Curtain act one. 14 Gambling man. 12 What is love. Gambling man reprise (Act II). 18 Ballet 2 - Reconstruction (sketch). 1 Overture (photocopy). 24 After Bonnie. Riverboat III 3rd tape. 17D-19A Riverboat sequence I (Two of a kind reprise). Riverboat III 2nd tape. Riverboat III 1st tape. Reconstruction Ballet 5. Underscore (Act II). 6C Galop + Waltz. [Riverboat sequence?] (pp. 1-34 missing). 6A 7A Reel (Stage band). 4A Tara (Gerald). 9A Waiting for Ashley Farewell. 7A 8 Two of a kind reprise. Quadrille. 22 Little wonders
    - [Gone with the wind. English & Japanese; arr.], 1 manuscript condensed score (333 p. in various pagings); 34-36 cm. (Box 29, Folder 198-201)
      Manuscript in pencil and ink (in part, photocopies)
      Note from discarded cover: Scarlett Tokyo orchestration sketches
      Score marked "Piano conductor"
    - [Gone with the wind. English & Japanese. Selections], 1968-1969; 1 manuscript score (304 p. in various pagings); 28-36 cm. (Box 30, Folder 202-205)
      Holograph, in part signed, in pencil and manuscript (in part, photocopies) with markings
      Miscellaneous music, including scores, sketches, and printed music
    - [Gone with the wind. English & Japanese. Selections], 1968-1969; 1 manuscript score (185 p. in various pagings); 35 cm. (Box 30, Folder 206-207)
      Holograph, in part signed, and manuscript in pencil (in part, photocopies) with markings
      Miscellaneous numbers, not in any order
      Note on discarded folder: Scarlett extra piano rehearsal music Oct-Dec 1969
    - [Gone with the wind. English & Japanese. Selections], 1968-1972; 1 manuscript score (132 p. in various pagings); 28-36 cm. (Box 30, Folder 208)
      Holograph, in part signed, in pencil and manuscript
      Also includes printed music
      Miscellaneous numbers not in any order
      Note on discarded folder: Extra music from
      English Production May 1972
    - [Gone with the wind. English & Japanese. Selections], 1969; 1 manuscript score (41 p. in various pagings); 31-36 cm. (Box 31, Folder 209)
      Holograph, signed, in ink and manuscript (in part, photocopies) with markings
      Miscellaneous scores, including some duplicates and published music
    - [Gone with the wind. English & Japanese. Selections], 1969; 1 manuscript score (67 p. in various pagings); 30-34 cm. (Box 31, Folder 210)
      Holographs, in part signed, in pencil (in part, photocopies)
      Includes sketches, scores, lyrics ([25] sheets; holographs in pencil and ink), and song schedules (photocopies, originals with Production Materials)
      Notes on discarded folder: Harold Rome original worksheets Scarlett Tokyo Oct. 1969 song schedules, etc.
    - [Gone with the wind. English. Selections], 1967-1969; 1 manuscript score (162 p. in various pagings); 28-35 cm. (Box 31, Folder 211-212)
      Holographs, signed, in pencil and manuscript in ink (in part, photocopies) with markings
      Includes miscellaneous scores, sketches, and lyrics ([82] sheets; holographs in pencil and typescript); also includes schedules and resumes of Japanese cast [copies, originals housed with Production Materials]
      Note on discarded folder: C work sheets Aug Sept Oct - 1969
    - [Gone with the wind. English. Selections], 1968; 1 manuscript score (58 p. in various pagings); 32 cm. (Box 31, Folder 213)
      Holographs, signed, in pencil and manuscript in ink
      Includes miscellaneous scores, sketches, and lyrics ([35] sheets; holographs in pencil and typescript)
      Note on discarded folder: Work sheets
    - [Gone with the wind. English. Selections], 1968-1969; 1 manuscript score (50 p. in various pagings); 28-31 cm. (Box 31, Folder 214)
      Holographs, signed, in pencil
      Includes scores, sketches, and lyrics ([21] sheets; holographs in pencil and typescript)
      Note on discarded envelope: Gone With The Wind - work sheets after preliminary score 1969
    - [Gone with the wind. English. Selections], 1968-1969; 1 manuscript score (101 p. in various pagings); 28-32 cm. (Box 31, Folder 215)
      Holographs, signed, in pencil and manuscript (photocopies) with markings
      Miscellaneous music, includes scores, sketches, and lyrics ([20] sheets; holographs in pencil and typescript)
      Signed note on discarded folder: work sheets - A Before Tokyo B - Oct 1969; Scarlett composer's work sheets A Before Tokyo 2nd trip B After Aug. 1969 Harold Rome [this is group "A" of work sheets]
    - [Gone with the wind. English. Selections], 1969; 1 manuscript score (38 p. in various pagings); 28-32 cm. (Box 31, Folder 216)
      Holograph, signed, in pencil and manuscript in ink (in part, photocopies) with markings
      Miscellaneous scores, sketches, and lyrics ([13] sheets; holographs in pencil and typescript)
      Signed note on discarded folder: work sheets - A Before Tokyo Oct 1969; Scarlett composer's work sheets A Before Tokyo 2nd trip B After Aug. 1969 Harold Rome [this is group "B"]
    - [Gone with the wind. English. Selections] Scarlett / Harold Rome. -- 1968-1969., 1 manuscript score (34 p. in various pagings); 31 cm. (Box 32, Folder 217)
      Note on title page: original 1st versions manuscripts 1968-1969
    - [Gone with the wind. English. Selections], 1968-1969; 1 manuscript score (37 p. in various pagings); 32 cm. (Box 32, Folder 218)
      Manuscript in ink
      Note on envelope: Scarlett deshons / Scarlett First version songs - deshon + copies Dec 1958 [i.e. 1968]